Hello, My Name is Rukia Njeri.
I am a Mother of Four and a Grand Mother of two who I currently stay with in this house.
I raised the two of my Grand Kids. We have been through a lot.
Their fathers, one is a drunkard and the other had stroke, their mothers died.
So when I was left with the grand kids I accepted and took them in.
And by God's Grace, I found people to help them.
The one in Grade Six is being assisted and so is the one in grade four, Hanan.
I thank God so much. Because I cried to God and told him I don't want these children to suffer.
When I took them in when their moms died, I had faith that God would open doors for them.
I believe God has done it and we continue to praise Him.
(Channah's Assistance on my part.) I have a small business selling charcoal and paraffin.
When I am out there at work I see a lot of people, I don't have stress or time to think about a lot of things.
All in all I am grateful I don't have illnesses, I have good health, I am over 64 years old
and God has kept me whole. I am grateful I am not sick.
May he give me strength to raise my Grandkids and see that they Grow and have good education.
That is my hope. Thank you